Guide to the Paul Revere Reynolds Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Uncataloged Correspondence
  - John Farquharson Ltd, 1956-1976 (Box 56-65)
  - Fassett, John (Box 66)
  - Fast, Howard "E.V. Cunningham" (Box 66)
  - Fast, Howard (Box 211)
  - Fast, Howard (Box 67)
  - Feifer, George (Box 67)
  - Feldzamen, Alvin N. (Box 211)
  - Fensch, Thomas (Box 213)
  - Ferguson, Charles W. (Box 213)
  - Ferguson, Charles W. (Box 68)
  - Ferguson, Hugh (Box 213)
  - Ferguson, Mavis B. (Box 213)
  - Fergusson, Harvey (Box 68)
  - Fick, Carl (Box 68)
  - Fielder, Mildred (Box 213)
  - Fincher, Jack (Box 213)
  - Fincher, Jack (Box 68)
  - Finn, William J. and Stanley K. Schultz (Box 213)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield (Box 69)
  - Fisher, Lawrence V. (Box 70)
  - Fisher, Leonard Everett (Box 70)
  - Fishwick, Marshall (Box 213)
  - Fleming, Alice Mulcahey (Box 213)
  - Fleming, Amalia, Lady (Box 213)
  - Fleming, James Thomas (Box 213)
  - Fleming, Thomas James and Alice Mulcahey Fleming (Box 70)
  - Fleming, Thomas J. and Alice (Box 71-75)
  - Flesher, Gerald (Box 75)
  - Fletcher, Aaron (Box 75)
  - Flexner, James Thomas (Box 75)
  - Foley, Charles (Box 76)
  - Follett Publishing Company (Box 76)
  - Foner, Naomi (Box 76)
  - Fonzi, Gaeton (Box 213)
  - Foote, Darby (Box 76)
  - Forbes, Murray M. (Box 76)
  - Forsyth, James (Box 76)
  - Fosburgh, Hugh (Box 76)
  - Fosburgh, Hugh (Box 213)
  - Fowler, Judith (Box 213)
  - Fox, George (Box 76)
  - Francis, Robert (Box 76)
  - Frank, Ann (Box 76)
  - Frank, Ellen (Box 76)
  - Fraser, George MacDonald (Box 214)
  - Frederica, Queen of Greece (Box 214)
  - Freeman, Naomi (Box 76)
  - Freeman, Neal B. (Box 76)
  - Friedman, Bruce Jay (Box 76)
  - Friedman, Nancy (Box 214)
  - Friedman, Philip (Box 76)
  - Frings, Ketti (Box 77)
  - Froeb, Jeanne (Box 77)
  - Froncek, Thomas (Box 77)
  - Fryer, Lee (Box 77)
  - Fryer, Lee (Box 214)
  - Fryer, Lee (Box 78)
  - Fuchs, Sir Vivian Ernest (Box 78)
  - Fuller, Elizabeth (Box 214)
  - Fuller, Samuel (Box 214)
  - Fuller, Samuel (Box 78)
  - Furth, George (Box 78)
  - G - misc. (Box 78)
  - Gagarin, Nicholas (Box 79)
  - Gage, Nancy (Box 214)
  - Galen, Nina (Nina G. Neuschotz) (Box 214)
  - Galen, Nina (Nina G. Neuschotz) (Box 79)
  - Gallahue, John (Box 79)
  - Gambit (Box 79)
  - Gantz, Charlotte Orr (Box 214)
  - Gard, Robert E. (Box 79)
  - Gardner, Joseph L. (Box 79)
  - Garfield, Patricia L. and Zalmon H. (Box 79)
  - Garland, Joseph E. (Box 79)
  - Garrison, Webb (Box 214)
  - Garrison, Webb (Box 80)
  - Gartner, Chloe (Box 80)
  - Geld, Ellen Bromfield (Box 80)
  - Gentry, Curt (Box 81)
  - Gentry, Curt (Box 82)
  - Gentry, Curt (Box 214)
  - George-Brown, George Alfred, Baron (Box 214)
  - Gerber, Albert B. (Box 215)
  - Gerbert, Steve (Box 215)
  - Gerson, Noel B. "Leon Phillips," "Philip Vail," "Amanda Darling," "Samuel Edwards," "Paul Lewis" (Box 215)
  - Gerson, Noel B. (Box 82)
  - Gerson, Noel B. (Box 83)
  - Gerson, Noel B. (Box 84)
  - Geston, Mark S. (Box 84)
  - Ghar Parau Expedition (Box 84)
  - Gilbert, Joan "Joan Sewell" (Box 215)
  - Gilbreth, Frank Bunker, Jr. (Box 215)
  - Giles, Janice Holt (Box 84)
  - Giles, Janice Holt (Box 85)
  - Gilliam, Harold (Box 85)
  - Gillies, Jerry "Joshua Dash" (Box 85)
  - Gilligan, Edmund (Box 85)
  - Gilmore, John (Box 215)
  - Gitlin, Paul (Box 85)
  - Giunta, Aldo (Box 85)
  - Glaskin, G.M. (Box 85)
  - Gleaves, Susan (Box 215)
  - Glyn, Elinor Sutherland (Box 85)
  - Godwin, Gail (Box 215)
  - Godwin, Gail (Box 216)
  - Gold, Lloyd (Box 216)
  - Goldberg, Lucianne (Box 85)
  - Goldman, Albert (Box 216)
  - Goldsberry, Steven (Box 216)
  - Gollancz, Victor, Ltd. (Box 85)
  - Gonzalez, Laurence (Box 85)
  - Gonzalez, Laurence (Box 216)
  - Goodavage, Joseph F. (Box 85)
  - Gordon, MacDonnell (Box 86)
  - Gorn, Lester (Box 86)
  - Goss, Madeleine B. (Box 86)
  - Graber, Richard (Box 86)
  - Graham, Alice Walworth (Box 86)
  - Graham, Frank, Jr. (Box 86)
  - Grant, Kay (Box 86)
  - Grant, Kay (Box 217)
  - Gray, Westmoreland (Box 86)
  - Greenberg, David (Box 86)
  - Greenberg, Judith Anne (Box 217)
  - Greenhaw, Wayne "Lee Reed" (Box 217)
  - Greenspan, Bud (Box 86)
  - Greenwald, Jean (Box 86)
  - Greer, Michael (Box 86)
  - Grey, Harry (Harry B. Goldberg) (Box 87)
  - Grey, Ian (Box 87)
  - Grierson, Edward (Box 87)
  - Grierson, Edward (Box 217)
  - Gross, Martin L. (Box 217)
  - Grosset and Dunlap, Inc. (Box 87)
  - Grove, Fred (Box 87)
  - Grover, John Carpenter (Box 217)
  - Gubar, Edward (Box 87)
  - Gurney, Eric (Box 87)
  - Gurney, Eric (Box 217)
  - Guthrie, John (John Brodie) (Box 87)
  - H - misc. (Box 217)
  - H - misc. (Box 88)
  - Haas, Joseph (Box 88)
  - Hadden, Richard M. and Frances (Box 88)
  - Haggard, William (Richard Clayton) (Box 88)
  - Haggard, William (Richard Clayton) (Box 217)
  - Hagman, Harlan L. (Box 88)
  - Halaby, Najeeb Elias (Box 88)
  - Haley, Alex (Box 88)
  - Haley, Alex (Box 217)
  - Haley, James L. (Box 88)
  - Hall, Richard (Box 88)
  - Halsell, Grace (Box 89)
  - Hamilton, Hamish, Ltd (Box 89)
  - Hamblin, Dora Jane (Box 89)
  - Hamblin, Dora Jane (Box 217)
  - Hamilton, Eleanor (Box 217)
  - Hands, Harriet (Box 89)
  - Hanfstaengl, Ernst F.S. (Box 217)
  - Hannay, Chip (Allen Hannay) (Box 217)
  - Hans, Virginia (Box 89)
  - Hapgood, Charles (Box 89)
  - Hapgood, Charles (Box 217)
  - Hardy, Melissa (Box 90)
  - Hardy, William M. (Box 90)
  - Harkins, James Anthony (Box 91)
  - Harper, Mary Elizabeth Vroman Gibson (M.E. Vroman) (Box 91)
  - Harper and Row, Publishers, Inc. (Box 91)
  - Harrah's project (Box 91)
  - Harris, Phyllis (Box 218)
  - Harris, Walter and John J. Reeder (Box 91)
  - Harvey, Everett R. (Box 91)
  - Hatch, John (Box 218)
  - Hauther, Brend and Kathy Crafts (Box 218)
  - Hawke, David Freeman (Box 218)
  - Hawkins, Peter (Box 91)
  - Haynes, Lincoln (Box 218)
  - Hays, H.R. (Box 91)
  - Heard, Nathan C. (Box 91)
  - Heard, Nathan C. (Box 218)
  - Hecht, Julie (Box 218)
  - Hegi, Ursula (Box 218)
  - Heinemann, William, Ltd., Publishers (Box 91)
  - Hejinian, John (Box 91)
  - Helitzer, Florence (Box 218)
  - Hellman, Geoffrey T. (Box 91)
  - Henderson, R.E. (Box 218)
  - Henkin, Harmon (Box 92)
  - Henry, Omer (Box 92)
  - Henissart, Martha and Mary J. Latsis "R.B. Dominic," "Emma Lathan" (Box 92)
  - Herschlag, Jack (Box 218)
  - Heyn, Ernest V. (Box 218)
  - Hicks, Edwin P. (Box 218)
  - Higby, Mary Jane (Box 92)
  - Higgins, George V. (Box 218)
  - Hill Earle (Box 218)
  - Hill, Weldon (William R. Scott) (Box 92)
  - Hillary, Sir Edmund and Louise Rose Hillary (Lady) (Box 93)
  - Hinck, Robert (Box 93)
  - Hodder and Stoughton (Box 93)
  - Hogan, Randolph (Box 219)
  - Hoggard, James (Box 219)
  - Hoggard, James (Box 93)
  - Holland, Walter (Box 219)
  - Hollander, A.N.J. den (Dutch agent) (Box 93)
  - Holmes, Lewis P. (Box 94)
  - Holmes, Wilfred Jay "Alec Hudson" and Eric Holmes (Box 94)
  - Homewood, Harry (Box 94)
  - Homsher, Deborah (Box 219)
  - Hopkins, Ginny (Box 94)
  - Hopkins, Joseph G.E. (Box 94)
  - Hornberger, H. Richard "Richard Hooker" (Box 94)
  - Hornberger, H. Richard "Richard Hooker" (Box 219)
  - Hornberger, H. Richard (Box 95)
  - Horner, Jon (Box 95)
  - Hosie, Stanley W. "Michael Stanley" (Box 95)
  - Hosokawa, William K. (Box 95)
  - Hosokawa, Bill (William K.) (Box 219)
  - Hough, John Jr. (Box 219)
  - Hough, John (Box 95)
  - Howard, Robert West (Box 96)
  - Howard, Robert West (Box 97)
  - Howe, George (Box 219)
  - Hunter, Mark (Box 97)
  - Hunter, Rodello (Box 97)
    (See also: Calkins, F.J.)
  - Hunter, Rodello (Box 219)
  - Hutchinson, Michael (Box 219)
  - Huth, Tom (Box 219)
  - Hyde, Dayton 0. (Box 98)
  - Hyde, Wayne (Box 98)
  - Hyman, Dick (Box 98)
  - Hyman, Rebecca (Box 98)
  - I- misc. (Box 98)
  - I- misc. (Box 220)
  - Idaho Writers' League October 1968 Conference (Box 220)
  - Inchardi, Jay (Box 98)
  - Ind, Allison Wilbur (Box 98)
  - Ingham, Richard A. (Box 220)
  - Iowa Workshops-- The University of Iowa (Box 220)
  - Iowa workshop (Box 98)
  - Ippolito, Charles (Box 98)
  - Ireys, Alice Recknagel (Box 220)
  - Irwin, Margaret (Box 98)
  - Irwin, Theodore (Box 220)
  - J - misc. (Box 220)
  - J - misc. (Box 99)
  - Jackson, Donald Dale (Box 99)
  - Jackson, Donald Dale (Box 220)
  - Jacobs, Helen Hull (Box 220)
  - Jaffa, Jeffry J. (James Adams) (Box 99)
  - Jahoda, Gloria (Box 99)
  - Jahonda, Gloria (Box 220)
  - James, Henry and William James- James Estate (Box 100-103)
  - James Estate (Box 221)
  - James, Howard (Box 221)
  - James, Howard (Box 103)
  - James, Stuart (Box 103)
  - Janeway, Eliot (Box 104)
  - Janeway, Eliot (Box 221)
  - Janeway, Elizabeth (Box 221)
  - Janeway, Elizabeth Hall (Box 105)
  - Jansen, Jann D. (Box 106)
  - Janson-Smith, Peter (Agent) (Box 106)
  - Jeffers, H. Paul (Box 106)
  - Jeffrey, Ransom (Box 221)
  - Jemison, Marie S. (Box 221)
  - Jennings, John (Box 221)
  - Jennings, John (Box 106)
  - Jennison, Kaye "Kaye Starbird" (Box 106)
  - Jennison, Peter (Box 106)
  - Jerstad, Luther G. (Box 106)
  - John, Owen (Box 106)
  - John, Owen (Box 221)
  - Johnson, Florence (Box 221)
  - Johnson, Janet Mathewson (Box 106)
  - Johnson, Patricia H. (Box 106)
  - Johnson, Patricia (Box 221)
  - Johnson, Vance (Box 106)
  - Jones. Elwyn (Box 106)
  - Jones, James (Box 106)
  - Jones, James (Box 221)
  - Jones, Jimmy (Box 221)
  - Jones, Paul (Box 221)
  - Jordan, Jan (Box 221)
  - Jordan, Mildred (Mildred Jordan Bausher) (Box 221)
  - Jordan, René H. (Box 221)
  - Judson, Jeanne (Box 106)
  - Junker, Howard (Box 106)
  - K - misc. (Box 107)
  - K - misc. (Box 222)
  - Kaderli, Elizabeth Land (Box 222)
  - Kaderli, Elizabeth Land (Box 107)
  - Kahn, James (Box 107)
  - Kahn, James (Box 222)
  - Kahn, Stephen and Evelyn Gruhfeld (Box 222)
  - Kainen, Juduth (Box 222)
  - Kaliski, Anna (Box 222)
  - Kamins, Jeanette and James (Box 107)
  - Kantor, MacKinlay (Box 107)
  - Kantor, MacKinlay (Box 222)
  - Kantor, MacKinlay (Box 108)
  - Kantor, Tim (Box 108)
  - Kaplan, Howard (Box 108)
  - Karney, Jack (Box 108)
  - Karlins, Marvin (Box 108)
  - Kaye, Ivan (Box 222)
  - Kaye, Marvin (Box 222)
  - Kean, Gerald (Box 109)
  - Keeble, John (Box 109)
  - Keeble, John (Box 222)
  - Keel, Charlotte (Box 222)
  - Keel, John A. (Box 109)
  - Keith, Harold (Box 109)
  - Keith, Harold (Box 222)
  - Keller, Gail Faithfull (Box 109)
  - Kelley, William (Box 109)
  - Kelly, Aiden (Box 222)
  - Kelly, Joanne M. (Box 109)
  - Kendrick, Baynard (Box 109)
  - Kennan, Erlend A. (Box 109)
  - Kennedy, Lucy (Box 109)
  - Kenner, Jim (Box 109)
  - Keogh, William (Box 222)
  - Keough, William (Box 110)
  - Kernan, Michael (Box 110)
  - Kim, Richard E. (Box 110)
  - Kim, Richard (Box 111)
  - Kim, Richard (Box 223)
  - King, Harold (Box 223)
  - Kirk, Ruth (Box 111)
  - Kirkendoll, Pat (Box 111)
  - Kirkpatrick, Smith (Box 111)
  - Klarfeld, Jon (Box 111)
  - Klass, Sheila Solomon (Box 223)
  - Klein, Daniel Martin (Box 223)
  - Kline, Steve (Box 111)
  - Kluge, P. Fred (Box 223)
  - Knopf, Alfred A., Incorporated (Box 223)
  - Knopf, Alfred A., Incorporated (Box 112)
  - Knorpp, John (Box 223)
  - Koertge, Ronald (Box 112)
  - Korr, David (Box 223)
  - Kraus, Hans and Curtis Mitchell (Box 112)
  - Kriger, Malcolm D. (Box 223)
  - Kubie, Nora Benjamin (Box 112)
  - Kuh, Richard H. (Box 113)
  - Kuhn, Edward (Box 223)
  - Kuhn, Edward (Box 113)
  - Kwitny, Jonathan (Box 113)
  - Kytle, Ray (Box 113)
  - L - misc. (Box 113)
  - L - misc. (Box 223)
  - Lacagnina, Arnaldo (Box 223)
  - Lacagnina, Arnaldo (Box 113)
  - Lamb, Betsy Beaton (Box 223)
  - Lance, Kathryn (Box 113)
  - Landress, Mike (Box 113)
  - Landry, Robert J. (Box 113)
  - Lane, Frank W. (Box 113)
  - Lane, Helen "Helen Hudson" (Box 113)
  - Lang, Allen Kim (Box 114)
  - Lang, Theo (Box 114)
  - Langewiesche, Wolfgang (Box 114)
  - Larner, Jeremy (Box 114)
  - Lasagna, Louis (Box 114)
  - Lasagna, Louis (Box 223)
  - Latham, John K. (Box 223)
  - Lawrence, Ronald D. (Box 114)
  - Laycock, George (Box 114)
  - Laycock, George (Box 115)
  - Leacock, Stephen (Box 115)
  - Leaf, Munro "Mun" (Box 115)
  - Leaf, Munro "Mun" (Box 116)
  - Leary, Timothy (Box 117)
  - Leecky, Berta (Box 224)
  - Ledoux, Nicole (Box 224)
  - Lee, Fleming (Box 224)
  - Lee, Ronald (Box 224)
  - Lee, Tsun-nin (Box 224)
  - Leffland, Ella "Osa Simonsen" (Box 224)
  - Leffland, Ella (Box 117)
  - Lehrman, Robert and Phyllis Elperin L. (Box 117)
  - Levin, Howard M. (Box 224)
  - Levy, Julien (Box 117)
  - Lewis, Clayton W. (Box 117)
  - Liepa, Alex (Box 224)
  - Lincoln, C. Eric (Box 117)
  - J.B. Lippincott Company Publishers (Box 117)
  - The Literary Agency of London, 1902-1906 (Box 170)
  - The Literary Guild of America, Inc. (Box 117)
  - Little, Brown and Company Publishers (Box 117)
  - Little, Brown and Company Publishers (Box 224)
  - Livingston, Joseph A. (Box 224)
  - Livingston, A.D. (Box 117)
  - Loeb, Robert H., Jr. (Box 224)
  - Logue, John (Box 118)
  - Lolli, Giorgio (Box 224)
  - Lomax, Louis E. (Box 118)
  - Lopez, Claude-Anne and Eugenia W. Herbert (Box 118)
  - Lounsberry, Alyse (Box 224)
  - Ludwig, Myles Eric (Box 225)
  - Ludwig, Myles Eric (Box 118)
  - Lukas, Mary (Box 118)
  - Lumbard, Eliot Howland (Box 225)
  - Lund, Doris Herold (Box 225)
  - Lund, Doris Herold (Box 118)
  - Lyons, Nan and Ivan (Box 118)
  - M - misc (Box 225)
  - M - misc (Box 119)
  - Maass, Walter B (Box 119)
  - Mabie, Mary Louise (Box 119)
  - McCague, James (Box 119)
  - McCague, James (Box 225)
  - McCaig, Robert (Box 225)
  - McCaig, Robert (Box 120)
  - McCall, Tom (Box 120)
  - McCall's Magazine (Box 225)
  - McCallion, Kenneth F. (Box 120)
  - McCallum, John D. (Box 225)
  - McCann, Kathy Godfrey (Box 226)
  - McCarthy, Shaun "Desmond Cory" (Box 226)
  - McCleary, Dorothy (Box 226)
  - McCleary, Dorothy (Box 120)
  - McCleary, Elliott H. (Box 226)
  - McClement, Fred (Box 120)
  - McCoy, John Pleasant (Box 120)
  - McCoy, John Pleasant (Box 226)
  - McCrae, Douglas (Box 226)
  - McCullough, David (Box 226)
  - McCullough, David (Box 121)
  - McDaniel, T.C. (Box 227)
  - MacDonald, Allan William Colt (Box 227)
  - MacDonald, Allan William Colt (Box 121)
  - Macdonald, Julie (Box 121)
  - Macdonald, Julie (Box 227)
  - MacDonald, Robert W.- Cooper MacDonald, Inc. (Box 227)
  - Macdonnell, J.E. (Box 121)
  - McDougall, Ruth (Box 227)
  - McDougall, Ruth (Box 121)
  - McDowell, Edwin (Box 121)
  - McDowell, Robert E. (Box 227)
  - McElain, Alan (Box 227)
  - McGovern, James (Box 227)
  - McGraw, Walter J. (Box 228)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company (Box 228)
  - McGraw-Hill, Inc. (Box 121)
  - McGregor, Craig (Box 228)
  - Macgregor, Wallace (Box 121)
  - McGuane, Tom (Box 228)
  - McHale, Tom (Box 229)
  - MacHardy, Charles (Box 229)
  - McHargue, Georgess (Box 229)
  - Machol, Libby (Box 229)
  - McHugh, Arona (Box 229)
  - McHugh, Arona (Box 121)
  - McHugh, Edna (Box 229)
  - McIntosh, Mavis-- Elizabeth McKee Literary Representatives (Box 229)
  - David McKay Company, Inc. (Box 122)
  - McKenna, Richard (Box 229)
  - McKenzie, C.J. (Box 229)
  - Mackenzie, Franklin (Box 122)
  - McKeown, Martha Ferguson (Box 122)
  - McLaughlin, John (Box 229)
  - McManus, Yvonne "Paula Christian" (Box 229)
  - McMenamin, Thomas J (Box 229)
  - McMenamin, Thomas J (Box 122)
  - McNally, Raymond T. (Box 122)
  - MacNeil, Neil (Box 122)
  - Macrory, Patrick A. (Box 229)
  - McShane, Ed (Box 229)
  - McShane, Mark "Marc Lovell" (Box 229)
  - Madoff, B. Jeffrey (Box 229)
  - Maggio, Joe (Box 229)
  - Mahoney, Helen Hall (Box 123)
  - Mainwaring, Dabiel G. "Geoffrey Home" (Box 123)
  - Majeski, Bill (Box 230)
  - Maloney, Ralph (Box 230)
  - Maloney, Ralph (Box 123)
  - Manalli, Fred S. (Box 230)
  - Manber, David (Box 123)
  - Maner, Alfred W. and David H. Buswell (Box 230)
  - Mangione, Jerre G. (Box 230)
  - Mangione, Jerre G. (Box 123)
  - Mangione, Jerre G. (Box 124)
  - Manheim, Mannie (Box 230)
  - Manheim, Mannie (Box 124)
  - Mann, Roderick (Box 124)
  - Manso, Peter (Box 124)
  - Mar, Shuhyin L. (Box 124)
  - Mar, Timothy,T. (Box 124)
  - Mar, Timothy,T. (Box 230)
  - Marais, Raymond (Box 230)
  - Marder, Irving (Box 230)
  - Mark, Norman (Box 230)
  - Markandaya, Kamala (Box 230)
  - Markandaya, Kamala (Box 124)
  - Marks, Richard Lee (Box 230)
  - Markstein, David Lee (Box 230)
  - Marsh, Robert L. (Box 231)
  - Marshall, Betty White (Box 231)
  - Marshall, Edison (Box 231)
  - Marshall, Edison (Box 125)
  - Marshall, Marguerite Moores (Marguerite Dean) (Box 125)
  - Martin, Ben (Box 231)
  - Martin, John Stuart (Box 231)
  - Martin, Mary (Box 125)
  - Martin, Pete (Box 231)
  - Martone, Roland A. (Box 231)
  - Mason, Herbert Molloy, Jr. (Box 231)
  - Mason, Herbert Molloy, Jr. (Box 125)
  - Mason, Herbert Molloy, Jr. (Box 126)
  - Mason, Paule (Box 126)
  - Matthiessen, Barbara Heggie (Box 126)
  - Maxwell, Evan and Ann (Box 126)
  - Mayo, Charles William (Box 231)
  - Meacham, Ellis K. (Box 231)
  - Meacham, Ellis K. (Box 126)
  - Mellen, Kathleen Dickenson (Box 231)
  - Mellor, William Bancroft (Box 231)
  - Melville, Keith (Box 126)
  - Meredith Press (Box 126)
  - Metalious, Grace (Box 232)
  - Metalious, Grace (Box 127)
  - Metz, Michae (Box 127)
  - Meyer, Lewis (Box 127)
  - Meyer, Lewis (Box 232)
  - Meyers, Joan (Box 232)
  - Michaels, Eric (Box 232)
  - Mickelberry, William (Box 127)
  - Middleton, Drew (Box 127)
  - Middleton, Drew (Box 232)
  - Miller, Ed Mack (Box 232)
  - Miller, Mike (Box 127)
  - Miller, Winton H. (Box 127)
  - Minskoff, Alan (Box 128)
  - Misurella, Fred (Box 128)
  - Mitchell, Joyce Slayton (Box 128)
  - Mitchell, Joyce Slayton (Box 232)
  - Mitchell, Marie (Box 232)
  - Mockler, Gretchen Travis (Box 128)
  - Modupe Paris, Prince (Box 232)
  - Moffat, Frances (Box 128)
  - Moffett, Hugh (Box 128)
  - Moffett, Hugh (Box 232)
  - Molloy, Robert (Box 232)
  - Molson-Stanton Associates Agency, Inc. (Box 232)
  - Monun, Meade (Box 128)
  - Molli, Jeanne (Box 128)
  - Molson, Gordon - Molson-Stanton (Box 129)
  - Associates Agency, Inc. (Box 129)
  - Monjo, Ferdinand N. (Box 129)
  - Mooney, Elizabeth C. (Box 129)
  - Moore, Gilbert (Box 129)
  - Moore, Nate (Box 233)
  - Moore, Sarah E. (Box 129)
  - Moore, Sonia (Box 129)
  - Moore, Sonia (Box 233)
  - Moore, Steve (Box 233)
  - Maray, Ann (Box 233)
  - Morgan, Beatrice Burton (Box 129)
  - Morgan, C. Stuart and Ikrima (Box 129)
  - Morgan, Lael (Box 129)
  - Morgan, Lael (Box 233)
  - Morgan-Sheehan, Patricia "Patt Stone" (Box 233)
  - Morgan-Sheehan, Patricia (Box 129)
  - Morgan, Speer (Box 129)
  - Morris, James F. (Box 130)
  - Morris, James F (Box 233)
  - Morris, Norman S. (Box 233)
  - Morrow, William, and Company, Inc. (Box 233)
  - Morrow, William, and Company, Inc. (Box 130)
  - Mortimer, Penelope Ruth (Box 233)
  - Mote, Wayne D. (Box 130)
  - Motion Pictures (Box 130)
  - Motta, Marcelo Ramos (Box 130)
  - Muldoon, Tony and Bob Hardy (Box 130)
  - Mulkeen, Thomas P. (Box 233)
  - Muller, Frederick Ltd. Publishers (Box 233)
  - Mumford, Rick (Box 130)
  - Murphy, Earl Finbar (Box 233)
  - Murphy Lawrence A. (Box 233)
  - Murphy, Lawrence A. "Steven C. Lawrence" (Box 130)
  - Murray, J.F. (Box 233)
  - Murray, Marian (Box 130)
  - Music Corporation of America/MCA (Box 130)
  - Mutrux, Robert H. (Box 233)
  - N - misc. (Box 234)
  - N - misc. (Box 130)
  - Nasaw, Jonathan (Box 131)
  - Nassar, Eugene Paul (Box 234)
  - Nathanson, Eric Mick (Box 234)
  - Nathanson, E.M. (Box 131)
  - Nathanson, Marianne Duest (Box 131)
  - National Interfraternity Conference, Inc. (Box 234)
  - Nau, Erika S. (Box 131)
  - Naughton, James M. (Box 131)
  - Nauman, Hilda (Box 131)
  - Navarro, Antonio (Box 131)
  - Naylor, Phyllis (Box 234)
  - Neale, Richard L. (Box 234)
  - Neary, John (Box 234)
  - Neary, John (Box 132)
  - Neill, Peter (Box 234)
  - Nelson, Jack A. (Box 132)
  - Nelson, Kay Shaw (Box 234)
  - Nelson, Kay Shaw (Box 132)
  - Nettelbeck, Colin W. (Box 132)
  - Neuman, Fredric Jay (Box 132)
  - The New American Library, Inc. (Box 132)
  - Newhafer, Richard L. (Box 132)
  - Niven, David (Box 234)
  - Nolte, Claude B. and Dorothy "Claude and Janet Lonet" (Box 132)
  - Nolledo, Wilfredo D. (Box 235)
  - Nordyke, Lewis T. (Box 132)
  - Norman, Geoffrey (Box 235)
  - Norman, Michael (Box 235)
  - W.W. Norton and Company, Inc. (Box 132)
  - O- misc. (Box 133)
  - O- misc. (Box 235)
  - (L The Observer ndon) (Box 235)
  - Odarty, Bill Lewis (Box 235)
  - O'Grady, Anne (Box 133)
  - O'Hara, Mary (Mary O'Hara Alsop Parrot Sture-Vasa) (Box 133)
  - O'Hara, Mary (Box 235)
  - Orr, Donna Reidy (Box 133)
  - Ortiz, Elizabeth Lambert (Box 235)
  - Osborne, Walter D. and Seville (Box 133)
  - Osborne, Walter D. and Seville (Box 236)
  - Ost, Marie J. (Box 236)
  - Ostenso, Martha (Box 133)
  - Oven, Lewis (Box 133)
  - Owen, Guy (Box 236)
  - Owens, Peter (Box 236)
  - P - misc. (Box 236)
  - P - misc. (Box 133)
  - Paar, Jack (Box 236)
  - Paddock, Paul E. and William C. (Box 236)
  - Paddock, Paul E. and William C. (Box 134)
  - Palmer, Lili (Box 134)
  - Palmer, Raymond C. (Box 236)
  - Palmer, Stuart (Box 134)
  - Palmer, Winifred Wise (Box 134)
  - Pan Books Ltd. (Box 134)
  - Paniagua, Lita (Box 236)
  - Parker, Robert B. (Box 134)
  - Parks, Wynn (Box 134)
  - Parks, Wynn (Box 236)
  - Parry, James (Box 134)
  - Pash, Boris T. (Box 236)
  - Pattullo, George (Box 134)
  - Paul, Raymond (Box 134)
  - Pearl, Richard M. (Box 135)
  - Pearsons Magazine (Box 136)
  - Peeples, Edwin A. (Box 136)
  - Peeples, Edwin A. (Box 237)
  - Peeples, Samuel A. "Brad Ward" (Box 237)
  - Peeples, Samuel A. "Brad Ward" (Box 136)
  - Pekkanen, John (Box 136)
  - Perutz, Kathrin (Box 136)
  - Perutz, Kathrin (Box 237)
  - Peroff, Frank (Box 136)
  - Peters, Harvey W. (Box 237)
  - Peterson, Frank (Box 237)
  - Petrow, Richard (Box 237)
  - Petrow, Richard (Box 136)
  - Pfarrer, Donald (Box 237)
  - Phillips, Craig (Box 237)
  - Pinckney, Roger (Box 237)
  - Pinsky, Mark (Box 237)
  - Place, Marion T. "Dale White" (Box 237)
  - Place, Marian T. "Dale White" (Box 136)
  - Place, Marian T. "Dale White" (Box 137)
  - Playboy Magazine (Box 237)
  - Pleasants, Henry, III (Box 138)
  - Pleasants, Henry, III (Box 238)
  - Pollinger, Laurence, Limited Authors' Agents (Box 238)
  - Porter, Eleanor Hodgman (Box 138)
  - Porterfield, Nolan (Box 138)
  - Porterfield, Nolan (Box 238)
  - Potter, Margaret (Box 238)
  - Poverman, Charles Everit (Box 238)
  - Poverman, Charles Everit (Box 138)
  - Powell, Lili (Lily Powell-Froissard) (Box 238)
  - Powers, Arthur, Harlan Jack Griswold, Mike Misenheimer, and Edward Tromanhauser (Box 238)
  - Powers, Arthur, Harlan Jack Griswold, Mike Misenheimer, and Edward Tromanhauser (Box 138)
  - Pratt, Elizabeth Stuart (Box 238)
  - Pratt, Elizabeth Stuart (Box 138)
  - Pratt, John Lowell (Box 138)
  - Preminger, Erik Lee (Box 139)
  - Prentice-Hall, Inc. (Box 139)
  - Prescott, Orville (Box 238)
  - Price, B. Raymond (Box 238)
  - Price, Vincent (Box 238)
  - Price, Vincent (Box 139)
  - Putnam's Sons, G.P. Publishers (Box 238)
  - Pyramid Books (Almat Publishing Corporation) (Box 238)
  - Queen, Ellery (Box 239)
  - Quinn, Frank H. and Beris "Patris Franquin" (Box 239)
  - R - misc. (Box 239)
  - R - misc. (Box 139)
  - Rae, George William (Box 140)
  - Rachleff, Owen (Box 239)
  - Randall, David A. (Box 239)
  - Random House, Inc. (Box 140)
  - Ranier, Peter and Ruth W. (Box 239)
  - Raphael, Frederic (Box 140)
  - Ray, Grace Ernestine (Box 239)
  - The Reader's Digest (Box 239)
  - Record of Sales, 1943-1954 (Box 239)
  - Redbook (Box 239)
  - Reddy, John (Box 239)
  - Reddy, John (Box 140)
  - Regnery, Henry, Company Publishers (Box 239)
  - Regush, Nicholas M. (Box 140)
  - Reid, Jan (Box 140)
  - Reinehr, Robert C. (Box 140)
  - Reiter, Bruce Philip (Box 140)
  - Rensberger, Lois (Box 140)
  - Reynolds, Betty Jane (Box 239)